welcome back to another audacity
欢迎回到另一个大胆的地方
tutorial in this video I'll show you how
教程在本视频中 我将向您展示如何
to work with multiple tracks and record
使用多首曲目和录制的步骤
audio over top of existing audio and
音频覆盖在现有音频之上 并且
play both at the same time maybe you
也许你可以同时玩这两种游戏
want to have a music playing at the
想在音乐厅放音乐吗？
introduction of your podcast and then
介绍你的播客 然后
you want to have your voice come in and
你想让你的声音进来然后
talk overtop of that music this is how
在音乐之上谈论这是怎么回事
we can do that so let's say we want to
我们可以做到这一点 假设我们想
bring in music first we have this jazz
先放音乐 我们有爵士乐
guitar music we looked at in the past we
我们过去看过的吉他音乐
can play it here what it sounds like but
我可以在这里播放它听起来像什么 但是
if I want to record if I move my
如果我想要记录 如果我移动我的
playhead to a certain point and hit
头球打到某一点 然后击球
record it starts recording my voice at
录制它开始录制我的声音
the end it like up ends my audio
结束它就像结束我的音频
recording to the end of this of this
录制到这段视频的结尾
track here so I'm gonna hit ctrl Z to
在这里跟踪 所以我要按Ctrl Z键
get rid of that and what we want to do
摆脱它 我们想要做的是
is actually add a second track if we hit
实际上是添加第二首曲目 如果我们击中
this little arrow here and minimize this
这里的小箭头 最小化这个
and we can see there's all kinds of
我们可以看到有各种各样的
space here we could add more tracks so
在这里我们可以添加更多的曲目 这样
to do that we kind of touched on it in
为了做到这一点 我们在
the last video a little bit at the end
最后一段视频在最后一点
we go to tracks add new and we'll go add
我们转到曲目添加新项 然后我们将添加
new stereo track so now we have another
新的立体声音轨 所以现在我们有了另一个
track here we could minimize it as well
跟踪到这里 我们也可以将其最小化
we can go track we can go add new stereo
我们可以去跟踪我们可以去添加新的立体声音响
track we can just get a bunch of
我们就能拿到一堆
different tracks in here and then we can
这里有不同的轨道 然后我们就可以
expand whichever one we want to look at
展开我们想要查看的任何一个
these things have nothing in them and
这些东西里面什么都没有
then this is our music if you want to
那么这是我们的音乐 如果你想的话
get rid of a track we just select it and
去掉一首曲目我们只需选择它
while we have it selected we can go
只要我们选好了 我们就可以走了
tracks remove track if we want to remove
如果要移除轨迹 请移除轨迹
this audio track we can just hit here
我们可以在这里点击的这首音轨
close and will actually close and get
关闭 并将实际关闭并获得
rid of remove that track as well and to
删除也删除该轨道 并
get it to come back we go edit undo
让它回来 我们去编辑撤销
track remove and now it's back if I want
轨道移除 现在它回来了 如果我想的话
to record over top of this now I just
为了超越这一点 现在我只是
click down here in this track to where I
在此路径中单击此处 转至我所在的位置
want to start recording and I hit record
想要开始录制 我点击了录制
it'll play the music and so I can hear
它会播放音乐 这样我就能听到
it and then I can talk and record in
然后我就可以说话和录音了
this track hello welcome to the podcast
欢迎收听播客节目
you can talk here overtop the music and
你可以在这里畅谈而不是音乐
it's pretty cool
这是相当酷的
then hit stop and now we have two
然后点击停止 现在我们有两个
separate different pieces of audio if we
如果我们将不同的音频片段分开
want so if we play it play back now they
想要这样 如果我们现在播放 现在播放
both play at the same time we can use
两者同时进行 我们可以使用
our time shift tool to move this forward
我们的时移工具来推动这一点
or back if we want it to come in at a
或者如果我们想让它以一种
different point in the audio
音频中的不同点
hello welcome to the podcast we can
大家好 欢迎收看我们的播客
apply different effects to this and do
对此应用不同的效果并执行
different things like that so yeah
不同的事情 所以是的
that's basically it and then if we want
基本上就是这样 如果我们想
to adjust these tracks we can click this
要调整这些轨迹 我们可以点击此按钮
here and we say move track up and now
在这里 我们说向上移动轨迹 现在
that our audio track is our kind of top
我们的音轨是我们最好的
track it doesn't really matter for as
跟踪它对AS来说并不重要
far as how it's being played back if
至于它是如何回放的 如果
this like this audio sounds like it's a
像这样的音频听起来像是
little bit loud for maybe me talking
我说话的声音可能有点大
here so we can lower the gain on it we
在这里 我们可以降低收益 我们
can do that while we're playing so it
可以在我们玩的时候这样做 所以它
doesn't change the actual wave form but
不会改变实际的波形 但
it does lower the volume in here also we
它确实降低了我们这里的音量
use like the envelope tool before which
使用方式与之前的信封工具类似
is a good example for this we click the
是一个很好的例子 我们可以点击
envelope tool we can lower down so we
我们可以放下信封工具 这样我们
can have this audio be kind of loud here
我可以把这段音频放大点声
then as soon as I get into the talking
当我一进入谈话的时候
point we can really make this audio get
我们真的可以让这段音频
really small and then as soon as I'm
真的很小 然后一旦我
done talking we can kind of bring it
说完了 我们可以把它带来
back up loud again if we want to see
如果我们想看的话再大声一点
that so now if we play this that's one
所以现在如果我们玩这个 那就是一个
way to do that in the next video we'll
在接下来的视频中 我们将
talk about using the amplification
谈用扩音器
effect and using different effects
效果和使用不同的效果
because we can actually use
因为我们实际上可以使用
amplification as well to change the
也可以通过放大来改变
volume make it louder or softer but I
音量使它变得更响亮或更柔和 但我
think I'm gonna end this video here
我想我要在这里结束这段视频
that's just using different tracks go
那只是使用不同的轨道围棋
ahead and play with that get familiar
继续玩吧 熟悉一下吧
with adding in multiple tracks and try
添加多首曲目 然后尝试
and record some mute some audio overtop
并录制一些静音的一些音频
of music yeah appreciate you watching
音乐 是的 感谢你的收看
hopefully you found this informative go
希望你觉得这段围棋很有见识
ahead and like comment subscribe and
前面和喜欢评论订阅
I'll catch you in the next video
下一段视频里我们会看到